Button, Daniel Evan; Papers apap231
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1965-1971; Undated; 5; 13.6 cubic ft.
  - Carlson, John - Department of Defense, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 64)
  - Carmel, Paul - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 65)
  - Carroll, Sheila A. - Department of Defense, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 66)
  - Castagna, Joseph O. - Navy, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 67)
  - Cavanaugh, Michael - Marines, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 68)
  - Ceglais, Ronnie E. - Internal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 69)
  - CG Selected Resolution Program, Button and President, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 70)
  - Cheeseman, Daniel F. - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 71)
  - Cheeseman Edward - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 72)
  - Chiofalo, Albert - Captial District State Park Commission, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 73)
  - Clark, Vernon E. - Veterans Administration and Veterans AffaInternal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 74)
  - Clemente, Brian F. - West Point, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 75)
  - Clemons, Mrs. Bruce - Small Business Committee, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 76)
  - Cline, Lawrence - Department of Defense, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 77)
  - Coffey, James J. - Discharge Status, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 78)
  - Cohn, Bernard - Commemorative Stamp, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 79)
  - Congressional listing and letters - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 80)
  - Corine, Donald - Judiciary, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 81)
  - Conklin, William - Department of Treasury, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 82)
  - Cooley, Edmund - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 83)
  - Coonradt, John C. - Navy, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 84)
  - Cooper, Wayne R. - Marines - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 85)
  - Cornell, R.H. - Selective Service, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 86)
  - Coscione, Anthony - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 87)
  - Cosgrave, Leo, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 88)
  - Couture, Noel - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 89)
  - Creiger, Don M. - Bureau of Customs, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 90)
  - Creighton, David L. - Department of State, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 91)
  - Crinnon, Raymond - Civil Service Commission, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 92)
  - Criscone, Albert J. - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 93)
  - Crocker, John - Air Force, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 94)
  - Cudmore, Pierce - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 95)
  - Cunningham, Christopher W. - Navy, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 96)
  - Dahlin, Donald - Navy, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 97)
  - Daly, E.R. - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 98)
  - Damon, Barbara - Congressional interns, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 99)
  - Daniel Button - Justice Department, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 100)
  - D'Antoni, Joseph E.C., 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 101)
  - Davis, Donald H. - Internal Revenue Service - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 102)
  - Davis, Richard H. -Montessori stamp proposal, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 103)
  - Dawson, Raymond - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 104)
  - Deventhal, Glenn L. - West Point, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 105)
  - DeBeer, Fritz - HEW, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 106)
  - DeLaney, Hazel and Boron, Marcus - Internal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 107)
  - Della Cioppa, Angelo S., 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 108)
  - Demma, Angela - Bureau of Census, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 109)
  - Denis, Joseph - Department of Justice, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 110)
  - Department of Defense, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 111)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 112)
  - Diamon - Veterans Administration, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 113)
  - Dollard, Michael J. - Departments of Army and Justice, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 114)
  - Donahue, Michael J., 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 115)
  - Donato, Nicholas - White House, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 116)
  - Droesssler, Earl G. - Commerce, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 117)
  - Duane, Robert G. - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 118)
  - Ducharme, Nancy - Department of Defense, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 119)
  - Ducie, Jerry - Civil Service Commission, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 120)
  - Duggan, Rita, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 121)
  - Dumar, Peter - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 122)
  - Dunaski, Paul S. - Navy - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 123)
  - Dunne, Hilda - HEW, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 124)
  - Dunne, William M. - Post Office - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 125)
  - Durham, Lawrence W. - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 126)
  - Dwyer, James J. - railroad retirement, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 127)
  - Dyjak, Louis - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 128)
  - Eckerson, Robert W. - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 129)
  - Eckert, Edward, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 130)
  - Eisenberg, Mrs. Hyman J. - Post Office, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 131)
  - El-Far, Munir - private bill, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 132)
  - Ellis, Benjamin - Civil Service Commission, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 133)
  - Enders, Jacob M. - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 134)
  - Eson, Charles - Commission on Violene on Campus, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 135)
  - Examination applications from U.S., Naval, Air Force, and Merchant Marine, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 136)
  - Fagan, John J. - Air Force, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 137)
  - Falasco, Stephen - Air Force, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 138)
  - Fazzio, John - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 139)
  - Field, Frederick K., 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 140)
  - Fischer, Linda - Department of Justice, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 141)
  - Fisher, Orville - Social Security Administration, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 142)
  - Fitzgerald, John T., 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 143)
  - Fleck, Joel J. - Navy - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 144)
  - Fleshman, Carl - Service and Exchange Commission, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 145)
  - Foisy, Daisy - Navy, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 146)
  - Foley, John - Navy, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 147)
  - Fowler, Roy J. - Navy, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 148)
  - Fox, Terrence M. -Department of Defense, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 149)
  - Frank, Stanley - Department of Transportation, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 150)
  - Freedman, Marvin - Department of State, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 151)
  - Friedman, Robert L. - Department of Defense, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 152)
  - Fuller, Earle J. - Library of Congress, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 153)
  - Fung, Jack - Immigration, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 154)
  - Gabrield, Henry E. - Inquiry, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 155)
  - Gade, Joseph - Treasury, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 156)
  - Gager, Warren - Post Office, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 157)
  - Gager, Mrs. Warren - HEW, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 158)
  - Garavelli, John - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 159)
  - Garvey, John J., 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 160)
  - Gerald MCNamara - USDA, 1970; Undated (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 161)
  - Gerfin, Helen Reed - Veterans Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 162)
  - Gifford, Lynn - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 163)
  - Gillooley, Thomas Jr. - White House Bill, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 164)
  - Gionet, David E. - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 165)
  - Giovanniello, J. - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 166)
  - Glamm, Lois, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 167)
  - Gleason, Joseph T. - American Federation of Government Employees, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 168)
  - Goodheim, Shirley - Watervliet Arsenal, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 169)
  - Gordon, Raymond D. - Department of Transportation, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 170)
  - Gorman, Donald - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 171)
  - Gould, Bruce - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 172)
  - Gould, Samuel - Conference Committee, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 173)
  - Grandy, George - Army, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 174)
  - Grant, Earl P., 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 175)
  - Gray, Raymond - Veterans Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 176)
  - Graziadei, Dominick, 1970 (Box 15 (5-Case Files), Folder 177)
  - Greig, Robert G. - National Weather Bureau, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 1)
  - Griffis, AFB - Air Force, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Griner, John and Gleason, Joe, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Grobecker, Richard - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Grosberg, Joseph E., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Gross, Eric T.B. - Department of Defense [Closed], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Gruber, Francis X. and Wright, Allan C. - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Halloran, Daniel F. - Committee on Interior and Unsular AffaInternal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Halpin, Dale F. - Navy - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Hanley, Representative James - Commemorative Stamps, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Harrington, Donald, 1970; Undated (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Hart, Leonard, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Hartmann, G.B. - Middle Tennessee Business Association, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 13)
  - Hartherimer, Albert S. - Department of Defense, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Healey, James - FCC, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 15)
  - Hebb, M.H. - Treasury, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Heckman, Joseph, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Heftler, John - Immigration and Naturalization, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 18)
  - Heller, Mary C. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Hennessey, Thomas I., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Herbach, David J. - National Guard Bureau, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Herbert, Edward L. Sp4 - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Herzog, Vincent - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Hickel, Walter J., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Hickman, Joseph - Navy, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Hines, Donald - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Hines, George D. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Hitt, Lawrence - Navy, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 28)
  - Hodgkins, William, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 29)
  - Hodsin, Barbara - Immigration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 30)
  - Hoteling, James C. - Navy, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 31)
  - Hurley, Harold - Selective Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 32)
  - Iommi, Luigi - Immigration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 33)
  - Isenberg, Herbet - Bureau of Prisons, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 34)
  - Jackson, Howard - Navy - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 35)
  - Jackson, Laverne, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 36)
  - Jefts, Philip Lowell - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 37)
  - Jones, Arthur F. State Department, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 38)
  - Jones, Donna - Overseas Teacher, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 39)
  - Jones, Everett - Social Security, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 40)
  - Jones, F.D. - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 41)
  - Jones, Peter - Department of Agriculture, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 42)
  - Joralemon, Clarence B. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 43)
  - Jurczynnski, Joseph G., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 44)
  - Justice Douglas, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 45)
  - Kalenian, James - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 46)
  - Kelts, Richard - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 47)
  - Kenney, Richard - Navy, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 48)
  - Kircher, Kathleen - Internal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 49)
  - Kiskis Foundation Littlefield, Robert - Internal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 50)
  - Klein, Robert Paul - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 51)
  - Klett, Michael C. - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 52)
  - Kmetz, Thomas J. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 53)
  - Kohn, Esther B., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 54)
  - Koonz, Gary A. - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 55)
  - Koppel, Alan - HEW, Evaluation Plan, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 56)
  - Kopschoc, Charles - Selective Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 57)
  - Kriz, Edward M. - Postal Service Commission, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 58)
  - Krugman, Erich - Civil Service Commission, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 59)
  - Kudon, Kenneth, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 60)
  - Kurtter, Robert A. - Summer Employment, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 61)
  - Lacy, Curtis W. - Social Security Administration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 62)
  - Lafar, Daniel - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 63)
  - La May, Robert C. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 64)
  - Lasher, Thomas - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 65)
  - Lattimore, Peter J. - Post Office, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 66)
  - Laudermilk, Agnes - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 67)
  - Lawson, Ivor V. Power Authority, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 68)
  - LeGere, Robert Q., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 69)
  - Legislative Counsel - bill draft, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 70)
  - LeVine, Harris D. Radioactive Contamination, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 71)
  - Liddle, Mrs. Charles M. - Department of Labor, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 72)
  - Liebich, Grace W. - State Department, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 73)
  - Lillis, Loren - FAA, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 74)
  - Littorin, Charles, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 75)
  - Loden, Peter C. - State, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 76)
  - Longo, L.J. - Food and Drug Administration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 77)
  - Lopez, Ingrid - Social Security Administration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 78)
  - Lorenson, David A. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 79)
  - Loveday, Theresa - Veterans Administration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 80)
  - Lucas, Anthony - FCC, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 81)
  - Ludwig, Wanda - Air Force, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 82)
  - Macarilla, Frank - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 83)
  - Madama, Robert R. Jr. - Immigration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 84)
  - Magee, William J. Jr. - Selective Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 85)
  - Mahoney, John W. ADJAN, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 86)
  - Malateda, William J. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 87)
  - Maletzky, Benjamin - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 88)
  - Mally, Edward - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 89)
  - Manning, Charles W. - Selective Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 90)
  - Mannolini, Luigi, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 91)
  - Marden, William - Department of the Interior, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 92)
  - Marsh, Kenneth - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 93)
  - Martino, Philip - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 94)
  - Massey, Frank - Post Office Department, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 95)
  - Martin, Timothy - State, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 96)
  - Mattice, P.C. - HUD, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 97)
  - Matulewicz, Edward, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 98)
  - Matzzie, Donal E. - Department of Transportation, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 99)
  - Maxwell, Thomas, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 100)
  - McClosky, I.E. - New York Employment, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 101)
  - McCrum, Richard M. - Air Firce - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 102)
  - McInerney, Mary T., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 103)
  - McNamara, Elwin C. - Treasury Department, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 104)
  - Medical Exams - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 105)
  - Miakisz, Thomas - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 106)
  - Michelson, Harry C. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 107)
  - Miles, Kevin - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 108)
  - Miller, David, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 109)
  - Miller, Edward J. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 110)
  - Miller, James - Air Force, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 111)
  - Mohawk flood control, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 112)
  - Mondore, Edward - GSA, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 113)
  - Mooney, John - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 114)
  - Moore, George Jacob - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 115)
  - Moreen, Thomas R., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 116)
  - Morrison, Daniel - Internal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 117)
  - Morrison, Robert C., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 118)
  - Moss, Michael A. - State, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 119)
  - Munro, William J. - Selective Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 120)
  - Munsell, Edward C. - Internal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 121)
  - Murray, Alfred - Marine Corps - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 122)
  - Nabozny, Anthony - Marine Corps, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 123)
  - National Council of Teachers of English, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 124)
  - Nelson, Sven D. - Air Force, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 125)
  - Neville, George, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 126)
  - Newell, Arthur A. - Air Force, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 127)
  - Nikolaidis, Simeon - Immigration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 128)
  - Noak, William - Post Office Department, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 129)
  - Noethlich, Hans, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 130)
  - Nolan, Arthur - Navy - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 131)
  - Norton, James - FHA, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 132)
  - Nottke, Richard W. - Navy - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 133)
  - Nowak, Joseph - Veterans Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 134)
  - O'Brien, James - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 135)
  - O'Brien, Michael - Peace Corps, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 136)
  - Occhialino, Joseph J. - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 137)
  - Oeser, Mrs. Robert, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 138)
  - Olson, Carl O. - Internal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 139)
  - O'Niel, Francis W. - Veterans Administration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 140)
  - Oppenheim, William - Air Force, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 141)
  - O'Rourke, Samuel - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 142)
  - Orvis, Laverne Esquire - Post Office, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 143)
  - Orzali, Arthur - HEW - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 144)
  - Paladin, Arthur Jr. - Civil Service Commission, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 145)
  - Palmer, Raymond James - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 146)
  - Papazogglou, George - State Department, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 147)
  - Parola, Terry Lee - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 148)
  - Pawelczak, Jan - Immigration and Naturalization, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 149)
  - Perkins, Arthur A. - HUD, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 150)
  - Phillips, Arnie - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 151)
  - Pickering, Dr. Richard - visitors waiver, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 152)
  - Pooler, Roswell - Social Security Administration, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 153)
  - Poskanzer, Edward - H.M.D., 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 154)
  - Potter, Leroy - Post Office, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 155)
  - The President, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 156)
  - Prince, Carl P. - Air Force, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 157)
  - Provost, Malcolm - Army, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 158)
  - Provost, Thomas - West Point, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 159)
  - Przyblski, Celia - Social Security, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 160)
  - Purello, Joanne - Navy, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 161)
  - Rajapaske, Reginald - Immigration and National Service [private bill], 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 162)
  - Recommendations and answered questionnaries, 1970 (Box 16 (5-Case Files), Folder 163)
  - Reed, Thomas C. - Selective Service, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 1)
  - Rexford, Don - Post Office, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Richardsin, Max C. - Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Richter, Alan - Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Robb, John W. - Department of Commerce, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Roberts, George H. - Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Robinson, Byron - Navy, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Robinson, Ernest L. - Ways and Means, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Robinson, Ralph - Department of Labor, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Romano, Louis A. - Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Rosen, David - Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Rosenbloom, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Rosenblum, Hyman Esq. - Weather Bureau, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 13)
  - Rosinger, Hilde - State Department - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Ross, Terry - Navy - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 15)
  - Rourke, John P. - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Rubino, Donald - Navy, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Russell, Gary - Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 18)
  - Ruszyk, Peter T. - Interstate Commerece Commission, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Ryan, Paul -Navy, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Ryan, Peter J., 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Saddlemire, Alan L. - Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Salhanick, David - Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Sanders, Richard - Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Sands, Dean Kennedy - Navy, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Sargent, Edward H. - State Department, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Savoie, Joseph -Army, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Schaefer, William - Immigration, 1970 (Box 17 (5-Case Files), Folder 28)